export default [
    {
        question : "What does HTML stand for?",
        options : ["Hyperlink and Text Markup Language","High-Level Text Manipulation Language" , "Hypertext Transfer Protocol Language" ,"Hypertext Markup Language"],
        answer : 3,
    },

    {
        question : "Which HTML element is used to define the structure of a webpage's header?",
        options : [" <header>","<h1>" , "<nav>" ,"<section>"],
        answer : 0,
    },
    {
        question : "Which HTML element is used to create a text input field in a form?",
        options : [" <input type='text'>"," <textbox>" , "<textinput>" ,"<textfield>"],
        answer : 0,
    },
    {
        question : "Which attribute is used to specify the URL where the form data should be submitted?",
        options : [,"submit-to" , "target" ,"destination","action"],
        answer : 3,
    },
    {
        question : "Which HTML element is used to create a table row?",
        options : [" <row>"," <tr>","<td>"," <th>"],
        answer : 1,
    },
    {
        question : "What HTML element is used to create a header cell in a table?",
        options : ["<td>","<header>" , "<th>" ,"<hn>"],
        answer : 2,
    },
    {
        question : "Which HTML element is used to create an ordered list?",
        options : ["<ol>","<li>" , "<ul>" ,"<dl>"],
        answer : 0,
    },
    {
        question : "What is the purpose of the HTML <ul> element?",
        options : ["To define a table","To create an unordered list" , " To insert an image" ,"To add a hyperlink"],
        answer : 1,
    },
    {
        question : "Which HTML5 canvas method is used to draw a filled rectangle?",
        options : ["drawRect()","fillRect()","rect()","drawFilledRect()"],
        answer : 1,
    },
    {
        question : "What does the HTML5 <svg> element stand for?",
        options : [" Scalable Vector Graphics", " Simple Visual Graphics","Standard Video Graphics","Scalable Video Graphics"],
        answer : 0,
    },
]